(Sheldon:)...nor the ability to use umbrellas.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
I gotta go to the emergency room.
(Sheldon:)Assuming you're correct
that your humerus...
(Sheldon:)...is no longer seated
in the glenoid socket, I would think so.
(Penny:)-Can you drive me?
-I don't drive.
(Penny:)Well, I can't drive.
(Sheldon:)Well, it seems we've reached an impasse.
Ow!
(Sheldon:)I could call you a cab or an ambulance.
(Penny:)No, no, no, I can't wait that long.
You gotta help me. Please?
(Sheldon:)All right. Let it never be said
that Sheldon Lee Cooper...
(Sheldon:)...ignored the pleas
of a damsel in distress.
(Penny:)No one's saying that. Let's go.
(Sheldon:)It does seem rather ironic that
for want of 99-cent adhesive ducks...
(Sheldon:)...we both might die in a fiery car crash.
(Leonard:)I wish Penny didn't have to work.
She loves camping.
That would've been great.
You and Penny having sex in the tent...
(Raj:)...while I sit out here
and watch Howard hump a cactus.
(Howard:)Okay, the best I can tell,
there are eight other campsites nearby.
(Howard:)Mostly science nerds like us,
but just over yon ridge...